diyatv.com 2014-04-17

# Diyatv.com | Terms and Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy for www.diyatv.com

What information do we Provided?

We do provide information to you in searching Entertainment TV Channels. 

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: Visitors viewing TV Channels. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

To process transactions

Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested. 

Do we use cookies?

We do not use cookies.

Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these 

linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

About TV-Channels Streaming

This website only provides any easy way to assess the online TV-Channel. No TV Channel stream is provide 0r produce by www.Diyatv.com.

Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at www.diyatv.com.

Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. 

** Disclaimer**

We are using third party streaming service to provide live broadcast. **Diyatv.com** is not responsible for any consequences and copyright law in any way. If you have any concern in this regard please contact

** DMCA **

The videos (Offline or Live) are collected and posted from YouTube and Justin.tv. If you want to Remove some video content from this website then immediately send an email to **admin** **@diyatv.com** , We can respond immediately.
